http://www.thenewsguard.com/site/privacy.html

Contact Us About Delivery
The News Guard’s Privacy PolicyTheNewsGuard.com, and the other newspapers and web sites of Country Media, are committed to protecting your privacy online. Not only does protecting your personal information help you, but also it increases consumer confidence and hopefully your participation online.The purpose of this policy to let you know what information we gather about you when you visit our sites, how we use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone and the choices you have about those functions.Our sites may have links to other Web sites. We have no control over the content or privacy practices of any of these sites or those of our business partners or advertisers.CookiesOur sites use cookies to verify subscribers and to help ensure single voting on our polls. Cookies help our Web sites recognize you as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while you were visiting. A cookie cannot get any other data from your hard drive, pass on a computer virus, or capture your e-mail address. We track the number of unique visitors to our sites and which articles or sections receive the most visitors, but not by any personally identifiable information. If you choose to modify your browser preferences to reject all cookies, you will have difficulty navigating our sites.Information we collectYou may be asked to voluntarily supply some personal information, including your name and contact information. If you choose to supply this information via the Internet know that we will never sell or share your personal information. We use the information you supply us to perform statistical analysis and marketing breakdowns. Some of our Web sites collect information as part of a reader advisory group. We may use that information to target questions of a specific nature to interested participants. If you elect to receive any of our electronic newsletters via e-mail or the e-mail breaking news service, we may use that address to invite you to participate in a readers group or some similar newspaper function.AdvertisersCountry Media, Inc. newspaper Web sites will perform statistical analyses of user behavior in order to measure interest in different portions of our Web site and to inform advertisers about how many consumers have clicked on their ads. We only disclose information to third parties in aggregate form. Personal information about you is not collected and will not be provided.E-mailNewspapers of Country Media, Inc. may occasionally use the e-mail addresses collected to send you promotional e-mail to its viewers about services offered by the papers.We may contact you regarding account status, changes to the subscriber agreement, and to confirm your login information.Accuracy of informationYou may contact us with any changes in your information, direct questions regarding our privacy policy, the accuracy of your personal information or the use of the information we collect by e-mail to our webmaster at admin@countrymedia.net. You may reach us by telephone at 1(800) 275-7799 or by mail at Country Media, Inc., PO Box 9278 Portland, OR 97207.Use of MaterialsThe right to download and store or output the materials in our sites is granted for the user's personal use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without the express written permission of the News Guard is strictly prohibited. Users wishing to obtain permission to reprint or reproduce any materials appearing on these sites may contact the Webmaster at admin@countrymedia.net.This privacy policy is effective as of Nov. 29, 2013. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time and will post those changes here as soon as they take effect.Web AdvertisingAdvertisers and third parties also may collect information about your activity on our sites and applications, on devices associated with you, and on third-party sites and applications using tracking technologies. Tracking data collected by these advertisers and third parties is used to decide which ads you see both on our sites and applications and on third-party sites and applications, but does not identify you personally and is not associated with your registration account.You may choose not to receive targeted advertising from many ad networks, data exchanges, marketing analytics and other service providers. You may also choose to control targeted advertising you receive within applications by using your mobile device settings (for example, by re-setting your device's advertising identifier and/or opting out of interest based ads). We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.---TheNewsGuard.com is owned by Country Media, Inc., 388 State Street, #800, Salem OR 97301.
Connect With Us
Trending This Week
Articles
Commented
ArticlesLincoln County on track for ‘extreme risk’ categoryPublic Health announces three workplace outbreaks in Lincoln CountyOffbeat Oregon: How Portland’s rabbi got in a gunfight at the President’s hotelWaldport man killed during burglary, homicide investigation ongoingPolice Blotter: Man trespassed from four separate locations in a matter of hoursTwo COVID-19 deaths, nearly 60 new cases has Lincoln County heading for the 'high risk' zoneOtis residents survive fatal crash on Highway 18Lincoln County classified as 'high risk' in new COVID-19 frameworkPolice Blotter: Driver cited after hitting vehicle, person in Safeway parking lotUpdate: No arrests made yet in suspected Waldport homicide
CommentedTwo COVID-19 deaths, nearly 60 new cases has Lincoln County heading for the 'high risk' zone (1)
We're always interested in hearing about news in our community. Let us know what's going on!
Submit Here
Subscribe to our publication today! Subscribe for just $60.00/year, or claim your FREE access if you are already a subscriber.
Subscribe
